bounceme.net 2008-06-16

# No-IP.com - The Dynamic DNS Leader

No-IP.com Privacy Policy

No-IP.com has drafted this document, which details how we gather and disseminate information, in an effort to demonstrate our strong commitment to online privacy. Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy. 

#### WE DO NOT DISCLOSE DATA TO UNAFFILIATED THIRD PARTIES

No-IP.com does not disclose customers' personal data, including email addresses, to unaffiliated third parties. We do use, and permit our affiliates and partners to use, customer data for several purposes, which are discussed in detail below. 

#### USE OF INTERNET PROTOCOL ADDRESS

We use your Internet protocol (IP) address for several reasons: to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Web site, to help identify you and your shopping cart, and to gather broad demographic information. 

#### USE OF REGISTRATION INFORMATION

Our site's registration area requires customers to supply contact information, such as name and e-mail address, and demographic information, such as your ZIP code, age, or income level. We use this information to send you promotional materials from our company and from some of our partners. However, users may opt out of -- or opt in to -- these promotional e-mail messages at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below.) 

#### USE OF DEMOGRAPHIC INFORMATION

We also collect demographic and profile data that we use to tailor your experience at No-IP.com. Based on this information, we display products and content we feel you might interest you. 

#### USE OF ORDER INFORMATION

When you place an order, No-IP.com requests information such as contact information, credit card number and demographic information. The contact information you provide is used to send you orders, company information and promotional material from our partners. You can opt out or opt in at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below.) Your financial information is used for the sole purpose of billing you for products and services. Demographic data is collected to personalize future visits by displaying the content we feel would interest you most. 

#### USE OF ONLINE SURVEY INFORMATION

To participate in our online surveys, you will be required to supply contact and demographic information. No-IP.com uses this data to send you information about the company. We might use this information to contact you as necessary. However, you may opt out of or opt in to our mailings at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below.) Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site and used to personalize future visits by displaying the content we feel would most interest you. 

#### USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED IN CONTESTS

To participate in our contests, you will be required to supply contact and demographic information. No-IP.com uses this data to send you information about the company. We might use this information to contact you as necessary. However, you may opt out of or opt in to our mailings at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below.) Demographic and profile data are collected at our site and used to personalize future visits by displaying the content we feel you would most interest you. 

#### PUBLIC FORUMS GUIDELINES

No-IP.com may offer chat rooms and bulletin boards. Please note that information that is disclosed in these arenas becomes public. Use caution in disclosing any personal information. 

#### SECURITY

No-IP.com features security measures 128-bit SSL encryption to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information placed under our control. 

#### CHILDREN'S GUIDELINES

We do not knowingly collect or use any personally identifiable information from children. 

#### OPT OUT/OPT IN

No-IP.com allows users to opt out of receiving e-mail from us or our partners. To opt out of our mailing list you can send e-mail to a remove mailing list. 

#### MODIFICATION OF THIS POLICY

No-IP.com may amend or modify this privacy policy at any time upon written notice from No-IP.com to customers. In the event of an amendment, No-Ip.com will provide an opportunity for customers to opt out of the new policy, either by email or by filling out a form on the No-IP.com website. 

#### CORRECT/UPDATE PERSONAL INFORMATION

No-IP.com allows you to change or modify your personal information by sending e-mail to a remove e-mail address or by visiting a designated customer service page. 

#### DISCLAIMER

This site contains links to other sites. No-IP.com is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites. 

#### CONTACT US

If you have any additional questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us: 

Vitalwerks Internet Solutions, LLC  
c/o No-IP.com  
9585 Prototype Ct. Suite A.  
Reno, NV 89521  
info@no-ip.com  
775-853-1883 phone  
775-853-1886 fax
